https://www.morovia.com/help/term-of-use.html

Home Products MICR & OCR FontsMICR E-13BMICR CMC-7OCR-A & OCR-BSecurity FontsFarrington 7B Fonts Linear Barcode FontsCode 128Code 39Code 39 Full ASCIIInterleaved 2 of 5MSI / PlesseyCode 93CodabarUS PostalRoyal Mail & 4-StateGS1 DataBarUPC-A/UPC-EEAN-13/EAN-8 2D Barcode FontsData MatrixPDF 417QR Code PCL Barcode FontsPCL Barcodes & MoreCode39 PCL Scalable
Barcode ComponentsBarcode ActiveX ProBarcode ActiveX LiteBarcode DLLBarcode Creator PDFLeo Free Products Product Sitemap SupportProduct ManualsKnowledge BaseCommunity Forums Support Policy PurchaseOrder FAQ CompanyAbout & Contact Us Help»Term of UseTerm of UseEffective Date: May 23, 2006Welcome to the morovia.com (referred to as "Morovia", "we", "us", or "our"
herein) Web site (the "Site"). By accessing this Site, you agree to be bound by
the terms and conditions below (the "Terms"). If you do not agree to all of the
Terms, please do not use the Site. Morovia may from time to time modify or
revise the Terms by updating this Web page. Your use of our Site following any
such change constitutes your agreement to follow and be bound by the Terms as
changed. If any change is unacceptable to you, your only recourse is to
terminate your use of the Site.OWNERSHIP RIGHTSThis web site is owned and operated by Morovia Corporation. (All Materials
herein are protected under Canada and international copyright laws and are the
property of Morovia Corporation or its third party licensors. All rights
reserved.) As used in these Terms, "Materials" includes, but is not limited to,
software, images, text, audio and all other information, displayed, contained
within, or accessible on the Site. No Materials may be copied, reproduced,
modified, displayed, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, sold or
distributed in any way, except that you may download one copy of the Materials
on any single computer for your personal, non-commercial use only, provided that
you maintain in such copy all copyright and other proprietary rights notices
contained in the original Materials. No right, title or interest in any
downloaded Materials is transferred to you as a result of any such downloading
or copying. You agree not to assist others in any unauthorized reproduction,
modification, display or distribution of the Materials. Unless expressly agreed
to by Morovia in writing, you may not create derivative works based on the Site
or Materials contained therein, in whole or in part. The use of any Materials on
any other Web site or networked computer environment is prohibited.IMAGESAll logos, page headers, images and graphics displayed on this Site are
service marks, trademarks, and/or trade dress (collectively, "Marks") of Morovia
or its third party licensors. Except as expressly permitted herein, using,
copying, transmitting, displaying, modifying or distributing any Marks in any
form or by any means without the express written permission of Morovia is
prohibited and may violate the copyright, trademark, privacy or other laws of
the Canada and/or other countries.DOWNLOADABLE SOFTWAREThe use of any Morovia, or the Software of third parties, downloaded from the
Site shall be subject to the terms and conditions of the license provided with
the Software. "Software" includes any files, images incorporated in or generated
by the software, and data accompanying the software. You may not download any
Software from this Site until you have read, and agreed to the terms and
conditions of the license provided with the Software. Without limiting the
generality of the terms contained in any such license, you agree that you will
not: (a) modify the Software (b) de-compile, reverse engineer, or disassemble
the Software, (c) remove any copyright or other proprietary rights notices from
the Software; or (d) use the Software for any commercial purpose, or any public
display, performance, sale or rental, except as expressly permitted by Morovia
in writing. Morovia retains all right, title and interest in and to the
Software, including all intellectual property rights therein. You download
Software at your own risk and assume complete and exclusive responsibility for
any and all losses, damages and liabilities that may result from the use of
Software downloaded from the Site.USER COMMENTSWe appreciate your comments, remarks, feedback, suggestions, ideas and other
submissions you disclose or transmit to us (collectively, "Comments"). You grant
Morovia and its affiliates a perpetual, irrevocable, worldwide, royalty-free
right and license to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create
derivative works of, distribute, publicly perform and publicly display (in whole
or in part) your Comments, your name and any related copyrights, moral rights or
other intellectual property rights.USER FORUMSMorovia may provide access to certain discussion groups through this Site as
a service to you. Discussion groups, by their nature, may contain offensive,
harmful, deceptive, misleading, inaccurate or otherwise inappropriate material,
and you acknowledge and agree that Morovia shall not have any responsibility for
the content of any discussion group, or materials or articles contained therein,
that may be accessed on or through this Site. You understand that Morovia acts
as a passive conduit for, and does not control, or attempt to control, any
information, data, text, software, music, sound, photographs, graphics, video,
messages or other materials, that you, or any other user of the Site, uploads,
posts or transmits to or through the Site (the "User Content"). Morovia may, but
is not obligated to, monitor or review the User Content and retains the right to
delete any User Content at any time. You acknowledge and agree that you are
solely responsible for any User Content that you upload, post or transmit to or
through the Site, including, but not limited to, its legality, reliability,
accuracy, integrity, appropriateness and originality. In no event shall Morovia
have any liability related to the User Content, whether arising under the laws
of copyright, libel, privacy, obscenity, or otherwise. You represent and warrant
to Morovia that you will not upload, post or otherwise transmit any User Content
to or through the Site that infringes, misappropriates or otherwise violates any
copyright, trademark or other intellectual property right, right of privacy,
right of publicity or any other right of any entity or person; or that is
unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, scandalous, inflammatory
pornographic, or profane, or that could constitute or encourage conduct that
would be considered a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability, or
otherwise violate any law or Morovia rule or policy.You grant Morovia and its affiliates a perpetual, irrevocable, worldwide,
royalty-free, non-exclusive right and license to use, reproduce, modify, adapt,
publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, publicly perform
and publicly display the User Content you upload, post or transmit to the Site
(in whole or in part) and/or to incorporate it in other works in any form,
media, or technology now known or later developed. You also grant each user of
this Site the right to access, display, view, and reproduce such User Content
for personal use. You represent and warrant to Morovia that you have the right
to grant the licenses stated above.You acknowledge and agree that you may not upload, post, reproduce, or
distribute any User Content on or through this Site that is protected by
copyright or other proprietary right of a third party, without obtaining
permission of the owner of such right. Any copyrighted or other proprietary
content distributed with the consent of the owner must contain the appropriate
copyright or other proprietary rights notice. The unauthorized submission or
distribution of copyrighted or other proprietary content is illegal and could
subject you to personal liability or criminal prosecution.LINKS TO OTHER SITESThis Site may contain links to other web sites ("Linked Sites") as a
convenience to you. Morovia does not operate or control any information,
products or services on the Linked Sites, and neither endorses or approves any
products, services or information offered at Linked Sites. You acknowledge and
agree that your access or use of any Linked Site is at your own risk.PRIVACY POLICYIt is our policy to respect the privacy of individuals who visit the Site or
provide Comments to us. Our privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy"), is
incorporated herein by reference. By accepting these Terms, you expressly
consent to the use and disclosure of your personal information as described in
the Privacy Policy.INDEMNITYYou agree to defend, indemnify and hold Morovia, its affiliates and their
officers, directors, agents and employees harmless from and against any and all
claims, losses, damages, liabilities, costs and expenses, including attorneys'
fees, arising from or related to your (a) User Content, (b) use of the Site, or
(c) violation of any of these Terms.WARRANTY DISCLAIMERTHE SITE AND ALL ELEMENTS THEREOF ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE,"
WITHOUT REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND. Morovia EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS
ALL SUCH REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING,
WITHOUT LIMITATION, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A
PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NO INFRINGEMENT. Morovia DOES NOT WARRANT (A) THAT THIS
SITE OR ITS CONTENTS WILL BE COMPLETE, UNINTERRUPTED, SECURE OR ERROR FREE, (B)
THAT THE SITE WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS, (C) THE QUALITY OF ANY PRODUCTS,
SERVICES, INFORMATION, OR OTHER MATERIAL PURCHASED OR OBTAINED BY YOU THROUGH
THE SITE OR (D) THAT THE SITE OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES IT AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF
VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. ALL INFORMATION ACCESSED ON OR THROUGH THIS
SITE IS SUBJECT TO CHANGE WITHOUT NOTICE.LIMITATION OF LIABILITYIN NO EVENT SHALL Morovia, ITS LICENSORS, OR ANYONE ELSE WHO HELPED CREATE,
PRODUCE OR DELIVER THIS SITE, BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL,
SPECIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, LOST PROFITS OR
LOST DATA) ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THIS
SITE, WHETHER IN AN ACTION UNDER CONTRACT, TORT OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY, EVEN
IF Morovia HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. MOROVIA'S TOTAL
LIABILITY FOR ALL CLAIMS ARISING FROM OR RELATING TO THESE TERMS OR USE OF THIS
SITE SHALL NOT EXCEED ONE HUNDRED DOLLARS (US$100). SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT
ALLOW THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL
DAMAGES. ACCORDINGLY, SOME OF THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.TERMINATIONYou agree that Morovia, in its sole discretion, may suspend or terminate its
operation of the Site or your use of the Site (or any portions thereof), and may
remove and discard any User Content, Software or Materials within the Site, for
any reason. In the event you fail to comply with the Terms , your right to use
the Site will automatically terminate. Upon any termination of the Site, or your
use of the Site, you agree to immediately and completely destroy all copies of
any Software of Materials downloaded form the Site. You agree that Morovia shall
not be liable to you or any third-party for any termination of the Site, your
access to the Site or any removal of any User Content from the Site.GENERALThese Terms constitute the entire agreement between you and Morovia and supersede and replace any prior agreements, whether written or oral, between you and Morovia related to the subject matter herein. The failure of Morovia to exercise or enforce any right or provision of these Terms shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. If any provision of the Terms is found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, the parties nevertheless agree that the court should endeavor to give effect to the parties' intentions as reflected in the provision, and all other provisions of the Terms shall remain in full force and effect. You agree that regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, you must file any claim or cause of action arising out of or related to use of the Site or otherwise arising out of or related to these Terms within one (1) year after such claim or cause of action arose. The section titles in these Terms are for convenience only and have no legal or contractual effect.CONTACT MOROVIA LEGAL DEPARTMENTFor further information on the Terms, the Site, or any other Web site owned and operated by Morovia, please contact Morovia Legal Department at:7725 Birchmount Road, Unit 42, Markham, Ontario, CanadaCOPYRIGHT STATEMENTThis site and the contents of this site, including but not limited to, text,
photographs, graphics, illustrations, video, sound, software and other material
(all such contents collectively referred to as "Content") are protected under
Canada and international copyright laws and are the property of Morovia or its
third party licensors. All rights reserved. Except as expressly permitted
herein, copying, distributing, transmitting, displaying, modifying, or otherwise
using any Content in any form or by any means without the express written
permission of Morovia is prohibited and may violate the copyright laws of the
Canada and/or other countries. You may view, copy, print, and distribute this
Web site subject to the following conditions: (a) the site may be used for
informational purposes only; (b) the site may only be used for non-commercial,
non-profit purposes and (c) any copy of this Web site, or portion thereof, must
include the following copyright notice: Portions of web site (c)2006
Morovia.com. All rights reserved.Note that Morovia retains all right, title and interest in and to all
software, products, processes and technologies described or made available on
this Web site, and all intellectual property Rights related thereto, and nothing
shall be deemed to grant you any ownership or other rights therein.On This PageOWNERSHIP RIGHTSIMAGESDOWNLOADABLE SOFTWAREUSER COMMENTSUSER FORUMSLINKS TO OTHER SITESPRIVACY POLICYINDEMNITYWARRANTY DISCLAIMERLIMITATION OF LIABILITYTERMINATIONGENERALCOPYRIGHT STATEMENTPolicies and HelpTerm of UsePrivacy PolicyOrder F.A.Q.Support & Updates PolicySoftware Return Policy & ProcessFont License AgreementComponent License AgreementLabeling License AgreementMorovia ProductsCode 39 FontsCode 39 Full ASCII FontsCode 128 FontsUPC-A/UPC-E/EAN-13/EAN-8 FontsInterleaved 2 of 5 FontsCode 93 FontsCodabar FontsMonterey Barcode CreatorFarrington 7B FontsPCL Barcodes & MoreMICR E13B FontsMICR CMC7 FontsOCR-A & OCR-B FontsSecurity FontsCode39 PCL Scalable FontsGS1 DataBar FontsPDF417 FontsQRCode FontsDataMatrix FontsMSI/Plessey FontsUS Postal FontsRoyal Mail & 4-State FontsBarcode ActiveX ProfessionalBarcode DLLBarcode ActiveX LitePDFLeoSignature Font ServiceFont Conversion ServiceCode25 FontsCode11 FontsTelepen Fonts © 2003-2020 Morovia Corporation. All rights reserved. Site MapPrivacy PolicyTerm of UseContact Us
